<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on NeurIPS 2024 Machine Learning Paper Review</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on NeurIPS 2024 Machine Learning Paper Review</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review of the Blog &#34;Unveiling the Power of Linear Transformers&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/linear-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/linear-review/</guid>
      
      <description>Review of the Blog &amp;ldquo;Unveiling the Power of Linear Transformers&amp;rdquo; The blog &amp;ldquo;Unveiling the Power of Linear Transformers&amp;rdquo; provides a solid introduction to the topic, outlining the computational advantages and novel capabilities of linear transformers, such as kernelized self-attention. The structure is clear, and the visual aids effectively complement the content. Key sections like &amp;ldquo;Why Study Linear Transformers?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Key Contributions&amp;rdquo; emphasize the main takeaways from the research.
One of the blog&amp;rsquo;s key strengths is its ability to distill complex topics like kernelized self-attention and recursive updates into a digestible format.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Tokens to Mastery: How AGILE is Redefining AI Decision-Making</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/agile-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/agile-review/</guid>
      
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) agents have come a long way from simply answering questions. Imagine a customer asking, &amp;ldquo;Will this camera case work for macro photography?&amp;rdquo; A good AI might say &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; based on product details, but a great AI would explain why it&amp;rsquo;s unsuitable, consult past knowledge, seek expert advice if necessary, and learn for next time. At NeurIPS 2024, researchers introduced AGILE (AGent that Interacts and Learns from Environments), a groundbreaking framework that teaches AI agents to think, adapt, and grow.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>This blog is part of our CSE471 assignment, where we will be discussing a paper from NeurIPS 2024. In addition to our primary review, we will also be evaluating two other related blogs.
Authors Wasif Hamid
ID: 1905026
GitHub: Wasif Hamid
Asif Al Shahriar
ID: 1905040
GitHub: Asif Al Shahriar</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
